[1,["ecpdLyjvZBwrvm+cedCcQy","f0BIwQ8D5Ml7nTNQbh1YlS","7a/QZLET9IDreTiBfRn2PD","2f6H6ieytIloCTh+BYn/LE","e4Iiec6zBFManBTwNNZGMk","69sy1DrC9Kf7UZ1RbO7xY2","29FYIk+N1GYaeWH/q1NxQO","3eUSaaGw1FZ5tsqBqPcnMS","a2MjXRFdtLlYQ5ouAFv/+R","3dJOzZHxpD5JTrzbNuNxzW","56BnevgcxM6oQg51maa3CW","71VhFCTINJM6/Ky3oX9nBT","cfJxLnGxRHXo5rfo11OTpB","fbdYDpnG9BL4ZpeATC5oCJ","2fIqXVF85DzLLZOj4PASTP","8eZ/zR/stBnYRwV9F3yE3b","a67MBd0LpMr7hL60Ho7v+P","18dB+O6D1K5poWYJ9KQEYm","43MnLB7e1F/KwcdsqnVgKa","f4nfR2SHVDEqaSxobkhNRm","caQSQXr2xKT4fidSQBszKA","69p0bNXplLOpPW9aa6SEj4","e7OHDgiVlCDKs6HscxZjtk","d2/545fPxDrbw2JWjttzxM","42piGNSatGxZiIcGVmOne1","804jzW2clIjanRxivg8zl8","27haAGRUVC4LiQQy5v//S2","fc0ibE62pNgamMIoUPcGLf","f5FWhw0OFB0L5yvw7UFRZX","8etEvCz15P44qn2BSA+zpa","2a6Tpv9flDD49GrchTMbiA","47bSGdduZJupJhqnjoQ/4y","62x5S+l2NHqqqQ/xGDv8Xb","1cq+ZfMAxBPYtWg3g2M5Xf","75q8tbDoZOe6BIvHUzqtlT","bdrI+tqS9K46C3Of8imyXS","c81DCOmapI55WQxM6AbNhd","11NGnVUUFO3LIph2zCDQtW","1dMZnG2qVLvITl3LubeCmc","0ep0JgHWhMgJZiodus3vIa","62CP2VOeBBW4lGZ2hOn3XU","88qqCOLoJE0ZxWvna1Jbjo","39IDe2VdFC86nYVUjLutqf","a0sNtKf39GbpK9Yzahy+qZ","1cU3i7PTNHwqoc1s8YcBQD","2eUsNtWx9PvJuUq39BKIMB","1akREGIFZD7YUgyfcb9vqh","ffDpHHVcZAhqOfy25Fe4w7","f34jvx70lDToiFWQFxWVOn","02delMVqdBD70a/HSD99FK","801KR6Bc1Ld4+EWADE2ELv","42i0ovL/ZKiaY4a+rEen6x","1ehWFBijZKq5v5gAnpIxqN","64JrxllXJEfrqF9WEPPUDf","19LT3wDo1E+IylcNL/M6TZ","e8Ueib+qJEhL6mXAHdnwbi","5aaUrHMvtCzqM1RV3fE3CI","35ZjGf3yZCJqGEvYNqOfj5","ed0hW5J5ZKBar1gflskoHO"],["node","_spriteFrame","_textureSetter","_parent","_N$skeletonData","_N$normalSprite","_N$disabledSprite","Animation_Titleback","Animation_Title","btn_NextLevel","promptBtn","resetBtn","questionLabel","levelLabel","uiManager","bottleMgr","btnResume","btnHome","btnClose","vibrationSlider","vibrationBase","soundSlider","soundBase","musicSlider","musicBase","btn_LevelComplete","tips_Label","btn_Close","btn_Jump","levelInput","scene","levelsData","clickBtn","clickClose","chooseBottle","waterFlow","waterDrop","victory","bottlePrefab"],["cc.SpriteFrame",["cc.Node",["_name","_active","_objFlags","_opacity","_components","_contentSize","_parent","_children","_trs","_color"],-1,9,5,1,2,7,5],["cc.Label",["_fontSize","_N$verticalAlign","_N$horizontalAlign","_N$overflow","_string","_lineHeight","_isSystemFontUsed","_enableWrapText","_styleFlags","_N$cacheMode","node","_materials"],-7,1,3],["cc.Node",["_name","_opacity","_parent","_components","_contentSize","_trs","_color","_children","_anchorPoint"],1,1,2,5,7,5,2,5],["cc.Node",["_name","_objFlags","_id","_active","_components","_contentSize","_parent","_trs","_anchorPoint","_children","_color"],-1,12,5,1,7,5,2,5],["cc.Sprite",["_sizeMode","_type","node","_materials","_spriteFrame"],1,1,3,6],["cc.Widget",["_alignFlags","_originalWidth","_originalHeight","alignMode","_left","node","_target"],-2,1,1],["cc.Button",["node","clickEvents","_N$normalColor","_N$disabledColor","_N$target","_N$normalSprite","_N$disabledSprite"],3,1,9,5,5,1,6,6],["sp.Skeleton",["defaultSkin","defaultAnimation","_preCacheMode","_animationName","loop","premultipliedAlpha","_playTimes","node","_materials","_N$skeletonData"],-4,1,3,6],["cc.JsonAsset",["_name","json"],1],["cc.SceneAsset",["_name","asyncLoadAssets"],1],["efb02+zpwxLgZg73ZMvA/P5",["node","btn_NextLevel","Animation_Title","Animation_Titleback","Animation_ribbon"],3,1,1,1,1,2],["cc.Canvas",["node","_designResolution"],3,1,5],["d7026U5nOtNLYAT8B4JQA2w",["node","bottleMgr","uiManager","levelLabel","questionLabel","resetBtn","promptBtn","levelsData"],3,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,6],["06005HI1i5GdJvsDArc4Nwz",["node","clickBtn","clickClose","chooseBottle","waterFlow","waterDrop","victory"],3,1,6,6,6,6,6,6],["8bf61YApwdIy4Z9LfEyIk2Q",["node","musicBase","musicSlider","soundBase","soundSlider","vibrationBase","vibrationSlider","btnClose","btnHome","btnResume"],3,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1],["7cdce1JrVZAxJjiQ4hlFliK",["node","levelInput","btn_Jump","btn_Close","tips_Label","btn_LevelComplete"],3,1,1,1,1,1,1],["cc.ClickEvent",["_componentId","handler","target"],1,1],["cc.BlockInputEvents",["node"],3,1],["cc.Layout",["_resize","_N$layoutType","node","_layoutSize"],1,1,5],["cc.LabelOutline",["_width","node","_color"],2,1,5],["cc.Scene",["_name","_active","_children","_anchorPoint","_trs"],1,2,5,7],["cc.Camera",["_clearFlags","_depth","node"],1,1],["d6d00MHtP5AMr8ecSVtsyDM",["node","bottleContainer"],3,1,1],["cc.EditBox",["maxLength","_N$inputMode","node","_N$textLabel","_N$placeholderLabel","_N$background"],1,1,1,1,1],["1b8e57isaxArpR5BOq+hYvW",["node","gameOverPanel","settingsPanel","promptPanel","promptLabel","promptCloseBtn","promptOkBtn","advertisementVideoNode"],3,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1]],[[5,2,3,4,1],[1,0,6,4,5,8,2],[1,0,6,7,4,5,8,2],[7,0,1],[17,0,1,2,3],[1,0,6,4,5,2],[6,3,0,1,2,5,5],[7,0,1,1],[1,0,2,7,4,5,3],[1,0,2,6,4,9,5,3],[3,0,2,3,4,5,2],[5,1,0,2,3,4,3],[18,0,1],[2,4,0,7,2,1,3,9,10,11,8],[1,0,7,4,5,2],[1,0,1,6,7,4,5,3],[3,0,2,3,6,4,2],[5,0,2,3,4,2],[6,3,0,4,1,2,5,6],[7,0,2,3,4,5,6,1],[8,0,1,2,4,5,3,6,7,8,8],[9,0,1,3],[10,0,1,3],[1,0,7,4,5,8,2],[1,0,1,6,7,4,8,3],[1,0,6,7,4,8,2],[1,0,3,6,4,9,5,8,3],[1,0,1,6,4,5,8,3],[1,0,3,6,4,9,5,3],[4,0,2,9,4,5,7,3],[4,0,6,4,5,2],[4,0,1,6,4,5,3],[4,0,1,3,6,4,5,8,7,4],[4,0,1,6,4,10,5,8,7,3],[3,0,2,7,3,4,2],[3,0,1,2,3,4,5,3],[3,0,2,3,4,2],[3,0,2,3,6,4,8,5,2],[5,1,0,2,3,3],[11,0,1,2,3,4,1],[12,0,1,1],[6,0,5,2],[6,0,1,2,5,6,4],[13,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,1],[14,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,1],[15,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,1],[16,0,1,2,3,4,5,1],[7,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,1],[19,0,1,2,3,3],[20,0,1,2,2],[21,0,1,2,3,4,3],[22,0,1,2,3],[23,0,1,1],[2,4,0,6,2,1,10,11,6],[2,4,0,6,2,1,3,10,11,7],[2,0,5,6,8,2,1,3,10,11,8],[2,0,5,7,1,3,10,6],[2,4,0,5,7,1,3,10,11,7],[2,0,5,2,1,10,11,5],[8,0,1,2,3,7,8,5],[8,0,1,2,5,3,7,8,9,6],[8,0,1,2,4,3,6,7,8,7],[24,0,1,2,3,4,5,3],[25,0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,1]],[[[[21,"levels",[{"levelId":1,"question":"如何获取1L、1L、2L、2L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":4,"target":1,"initial":4},{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":1,"target":1,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"E","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"E"}]},{"levelId":2,"question":"如何获取6L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":8},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":4,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":3,"question":"如何获取3L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":7,"initial":9},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":4,"question":"如何获取4L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":5,"question":"如何获取9L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":8},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":6,"question":"如何获取5L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":8,"target":5,"initial":4},{"capacity":6,"target":4,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":7,"question":"如何获取2L、7L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":3},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":8,"question":"如何获取5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":1},{"capacity":5,"target":3,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":9,"question":"如何获取5L、7L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":10},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":3},{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":10,"question":"如何获取4L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":4,"initial":5},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":11,"question":"如何获取4L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":12,"question":"如何获取4L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":6,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":13,"question":"如何获取8L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":7},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":3},{"capacity":6,"target":4,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":14,"question":"如何获取5L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":0,"initial":4},{"capacity":6,"target":5,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":15,"question":"如何获取6L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":5},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":7},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":16,"question":"如何获取5L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":17,"question":"如何获取2L、5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":18,"question":"如何获取3L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":19,"question":"如何获取4L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":1},{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":20,"question":"如何获取2L、4L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":1,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":21,"question":"如何获取8L、1L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":1,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":22,"question":"如何获取2L、6L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":9},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":23,"question":"如何获取3L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":24,"question":"如何获取7L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":5,"target":2,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":25,"question":"如何获取10L、1L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10},{"capacity":7,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":2,"target":1,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":26,"question":"如何获取5L、3L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":5,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":27,"question":"如何获取4L、2L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":5},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":28,"question":"如何获取9L、1L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":5},{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":3},{"capacity":6,"target":4,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":29,"question":"如何获取3L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":2},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":30,"question":"如何获取6L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":6,"initial":7},{"capacity":2,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":8,"target":0,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":31,"question":"如何获取6L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":6,"initial":1},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":9}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":32,"question":"如何获取2L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":3},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":33,"question":"如何获取2L、4L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":7,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":34,"question":"如何获取5L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":8,"target":5,"initial":6},{"capacity":7,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":35,"question":"如何获取2L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":36,"question":"如何获取3L、1L、10L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":37,"question":"如何获取2L、3L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":6,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":38,"question":"如何获取1L、2L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":1,"initial":4},{"capacity":8,"target":2,"initial":6},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":39,"question":"如何获取10L、1L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":9},{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":4},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":40,"question":"如何获取6L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":8},{"capacity":5,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":41,"question":"如何获取8L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":6},{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":42,"question":"如何获取2L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":3},{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":4},{"capacity":7,"target":6,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":43,"question":"如何获取5L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":7},{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":44,"question":"如何获取4L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":8},{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":45,"question":"如何获取1L、2L、10L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":10},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":46,"question":"如何获取1L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":47,"question":"如何获取3L、9L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":48,"question":"如何获取7L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":49,"question":"如何获取3L、2L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":50,"question":"如何获取6L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":8},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":51,"question":"如何获取5L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":4},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":52,"question":"如何获取8L、2L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":9},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":53,"question":"如何获取4L、2L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":5},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":54,"question":"如何获取1L、8L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":7},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":55,"question":"如何获取10L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10},{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":2},{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":56,"question":"如何获取4L、2L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":57,"question":"如何获取5L、2L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":58,"question":"如何获取1L、6L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":6,"target":6,"initial":6},{"capacity":4,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":59,"question":"如何获取3L、3L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":5},{"capacity":4,"target":4,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":60,"question":"如何获取10L、1L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":5},{"capacity":7,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":5,"target":1,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":61,"question":"如何获取1L、1L、10L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":1,"initial":5},{"capacity":7,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":62,"question":"如何获取9L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":10},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":63,"question":"如何获取4L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":9}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":64,"question":"如何获取3L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":9},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":65,"question":"如何获取4L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":10},{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":66,"question":"如何获取9L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":0},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":67,"question":"如何获取6L、1L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":8},{"capacity":5,"target":5,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":68,"question":"如何获取4L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":5},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":69,"question":"如何获取6L、3L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":10},{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":70,"question":"如何获取6L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":4},{"capacity":5,"target":5,"initial":0},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":1},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":71,"question":"如何获取2L、2L、7L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":2,"initial":3},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":7,"target":4,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":72,"question":"如何获取3L、7L、1L、9L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":8},{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":73,"question":"如何获取2L、6L、5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":2,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":8},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":74,"question":"如何获取3L、10L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":9},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":1},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":75,"question":"如何获取5L、3L、2L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":5,"initial":3},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":6},{"capacity":4,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":76,"question":"如何获取7L、6L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":8,"target":6,"initial":7},{"capacity":8,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":77,"question":"如何获取8L、4L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":5},{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":78,"question":"如何获取4L、1L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":1},{"capacity":4,"target":1,"initial":4},{"capacity":8,"target":7,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":79,"question":"如何获取1L、1L、6L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":8},{"capacity":6,"target":6,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":80,"question":"如何获取2L、7L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":5,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":6},{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":81,"question":"如何获取1L、9L、2L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":2,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":6},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":1,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":82,"question":"如何获取6L、2L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":0},{"capacity":5,"target":2,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":7},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":83,"question":"如何获取7L、4L、9L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":7,"initial":7},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":5},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":84,"question":"如何获取6L、3L、3L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":4},{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":4,"target":4,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":85,"question":"如何获取2L、2L、5L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":5,"target":5,"initial":5},{"capacity":5,"target":1,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":86,"question":"如何获取5L、1L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":9},{"capacity":8,"target":5,"initial":1},{"capacity":3,"target":1,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":87,"question":"如何获取4L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":4,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":4,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":88,"question":"如何获取3L、6L、6L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":4,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":6,"initial":5},{"capacity":6,"target":6,"initial":4},{"capacity":7,"target":2,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":89,"question":"如何获取6L、2L、5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":9},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":6}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":90,"question":"如何获取5L、6L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":6},{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":91,"question":"如何获取3L、5L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":7,"target":3,"initial":0},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":8},{"capacity":9,"target":8,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":92,"question":"如何获取1L、7L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":3,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":7,"target":7,"initial":5},{"capacity":5,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":93,"question":"如何获取4L、4L、7L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":4,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":7},{"capacity":9,"target":1,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":94,"question":"如何获取4L、5L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":95,"question":"如何获取2L、5L、10L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":6,"target":2,"initial":5},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10},{"capacity":4,"target":1,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":96,"question":"如何获取8L、4L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":8},{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":97,"question":"如何获取5L、2L、2L、9L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":7},{"capacity":4,"target":2,"initial":4},{"capacity":6,"target":2,"initial":3},{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":98,"question":"如何获取9L、5L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":3},{"capacity":5,"target":5,"initial":4},{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":9},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":4}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":99,"question":"如何获取3L、6L、9L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":5},{"capacity":9,"target":9,"initial":9},{"capacity":2,"target":1,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":100,"question":"如何获取4L、4L、7L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":7},{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":0},{"capacity":8,"target":7,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":101,"question":"如何获取4L、2L、2L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":8},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":0},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":102,"question":"如何获取5L、3L、4L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":5,"initial":2},{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":1},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":5}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":103,"question":"如何获取10L、4L、3L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":6},{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":3},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":104,"question":"如何获取4L、10L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":4,"initial":8},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":9},{"capacity":9,"target":0,"initial":0},{"capacity":9,"target":3,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":105,"question":"如何获取2L、6L、8L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":2,"initial":4},{"capacity":8,"target":6,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":10},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":106,"question":"如何获取5L、4L、4L、8L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":10},{"capacity":5,"target":4,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":107,"question":"如何获取7L、5L、5L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":7,"initial":1},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":9},{"capacity":9,"target":5,"initial":8},{"capacity":2,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":108,"question":"如何获取2L、8L、1L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":3},{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":6},{"capacity":8,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":3,"target":1,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":109,"question":"如何获取3L、5L、3L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":5,"initial":6},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":1},{"capacity":3,"target":3,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":110,"question":"如何获取3L、9L、9L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":0},{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":9,"initial":7},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":7}],"solution":[{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":111,"question":"如何获取10L、3L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":6},{"capacity":8,"target":3,"initial":4},{"capacity":3,"target":1,"initial":3},{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":112,"question":"如何获取3L、5L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":3,"initial":10},{"capacity":6,"target":5,"initial":1},{"capacity":6,"target":0,"initial":1},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":113,"question":"如何获取6L、5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":10},{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":6,"target":5,"initial":1},{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":114,"question":"如何获取7L、5L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":0},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":3},{"capacity":7,"target":5,"initial":6},{"capacity":5,"target":0,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":115,"question":"如何获取7L、10L、1L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":9,"target":7,"initial":7},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":10},{"capacity":8,"target":1,"initial":2},{"capacity":3,"target":2,"initial":1}],"solution":[{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"B"}]},{"levelId":116,"question":"如何获取7L、10L、2L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":9},{"capacity":10,"target":10,"initial":9},{"capacity":7,"target":2,"initial":1},{"capacity":7,"target":0,"initial":0}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"}]},{"levelId":117,"question":"如何获取7L、1L、6L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":7,"initial":4},{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":0},{"capacity":3,"target":0,"initial":2},{"capacity":10,"target":6,"initial":8}],"solution":[{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"C","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"}]},{"levelId":118,"question":"如何获取4L、4L、8L、1L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":4,"initial":10},{"capacity":8,"target":4,"initial":2},{"capacity":8,"target":8,"initial":3},{"capacity":10,"target":1,"initial":2}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"D"},{"from":"A","to":"C"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"A"},{"from":"A","to":"C"}]},{"levelId":119,"question":"如何获取8L、5L、3L水？","bottleConfigs":[{"capacity":10,"target":0,"initial":10},{"capacity":10,"target":8,"initial":0},{"capacity":6,"target":5,"initial":3},{"capacity":6,"target":3,"initial":3}],"solution":[{"from":"A","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"D"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"C","to":"A"},{"from":"B","to":"C"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"},{"from":"D","to":"B"},{"from":"A","to":"D"}]}]]],0,0,[],[],[]],[[{"name":"resetBtn","rect":[0,0,162,177],"offset":[0,0.5],"originalSize":[162,178],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[10]],[[{"name":"default_btn_disabled","rect":[0,0,40,40],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[40,40],"capInsets":[12,12,12,12]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[11]],[[{"name":"closeBtn","rect":[0,0,45,45],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[45,45],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[12]],[[{"name":"btn_ok","rect":[0,0,357,137],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[357,137],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[13]],[[{"name":"advertisementVideo","rect":[0,0,66,50],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[66,50],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[14]],[[{"name":"bg_level","rect":[0,0,207,60],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[207,60],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[15]],[[[22,"BottlePuzzle",null],[14,"bg",[-2,-3,-4,-5,-6,-7,-8,-9,-10,-11],[[0,-1,[91],92]],[5,750,1671]],[15,"gameoverPnl",false,1,[-18,-19,-20,-21,-22,-23,-24,-25],[[39,-17,-16,-15,-14,[-12,-13]]],[5,750,1670]],[23,"bg",[-27,-28,-29,-30,-31,-32,-33,-34,-35],[[0,-26,[71],72]],[5,605,682],[0,131.316,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[29,"Canvas","7d81EB00NKMqi/jZg+CDmX",[-47,1],[[[40,-36,[5,750,1670]],[41,45,-37],[43,-44,-43,-42,-41,-40,-39,-38,93],-45,[44,-46,94,95,96,97,98,99]],4,4,4,1,4],[5,750,1670],[375,835,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[24,"SettingPanel",false,1,[-58,3],[[45,-57,-56,-55,-54,-53,-52,-51,-50,-49,-48]],[0,130,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[25,"testPnl",1,[-65,-66,-67,-68,-69],[[46,-64,-63,-62,-61,-60,-59]],[-284.592,634.402,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[14,"prompt_bg",[-71,-72,-73,-74],[[0,-70,[23],24]],[5,703,744]],[2,"promptBtn",1,[-77],[[0,-75,[8],9],[3,-76]],[5,163,177],[125,-700,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[2,"Btn_Music",3,[-80,-81],[[0,-78,[53],54],[7,-79,[[4,"8bf61YApwdIy4Z9LfEyIk2Q","onClickMusic",5]]]],[5,199,66],[100,100.387,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"Btn_Sound",3,[-84,-85],[[0,-82,[59],60],[7,-83,[[4,"8bf61YApwdIy4Z9LfEyIk2Q","onClickSound",5]]]],[5,199,66],[100,-31.316,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"Btn_Vibration",3,[-88,-89],[[0,-86,[65],66],[7,-87,[[4,"8bf61YApwdIy4Z9LfEyIk2Q","onClickVibration",5]]]],[5,199,66],[100,-169.898,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[34,"New EditBox",6,[-91,-92,-93],[-90],[5,160,40]],[8,"Background",512,[-96],[[11,1,0,-94,[76],77],[6,0,45,100,40,-95]],[5,100,40]],[8,"Background",512,[-99],[[11,1,0,-97,[81],82],[6,0,45,100,40,-98]],[5,100,40]],[8,"Background",512,[-102],[[11,1,0,-100,[86],87],[6,0,45,100,40,-101]],[5,100,40]],[1,"resetBtn",1,[[0,-103,[2],3],[3,-104]],[5,162,177],[-125,-700,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[2,"advertisementVideo_bg",8,[-106],[[0,-105,[6],7]],[5,53,53],[62.031,74.802,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[15,"promptPnl",false,1,[7],[[12,-107]],[5,750,1670]],[1,"closeBtn",7,[[0,-108,[18],19],[3,-109]],[5,45,45],[296.201,296.201,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[1,"okBtn",7,[[0,-110,[20],21],[3,-111]],[5,357,137],[0,-480.249,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[1,"nextLevelBtn",2,[[0,-112,[35],36],[3,-113]],[5,353,133],[0,-368.296,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[26,"mask",150,5,[[17,0,-114,[37],38],[42,45,1500,2500,-115,4],[12,-116]],[4,4278190080],[5,750,1670],[0,-130,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"Btn_Close",3,[[0,-117,[47],48],[3,-118]],[5,45,45],[250.203,265.407,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"GameBtns",3,[-120,-121],[[48,1,1,-119,[5,355,200]]],[5,355,200],[0,-446.174,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"Btn_Home",24,[[0,-122,[67],68],[3,-123]],[5,355,134],[0,33,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[27,"Btn_Resume",false,24,[[0,-124,[69],70],[3,-125]],[5,355,134],[177.5,33,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"jumpBtn",6,[13],[[19,-126,[4,4293322470],[4,3363338360],13,78,79]],[5,100,40],[136.367,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"closeBtn",6,[14],[[19,-127,[4,4293322470],[4,3363338360],14,83,84]],[5,100,40],[243.089,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[2,"levelCompleteBtn",6,[15],[[47,-128,[[4,"7cdce1JrVZAxJjiQ4hlFliK","onLevelCompleteClick",6]],[4,4293322470],[4,3363338360],15,88,89]],[5,100,40],[-29.243,-46.788,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[10,"bottleContainer",1,[-129],[5,750,0],[0,-122,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"settingBtn",1,[[0,-130,[0],1],[7,-131,[[4,"1b8e57isaxArpR5BOq+hYvW","onClickSettingBtn",4]]]],[5,76,76],[-297.722,715.856,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]],[2,"levelLabel_bg",1,[-133],[[0,-132,[11],12]],[5,207,60],[0,700,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[30,"levelLabel",32,[[-134,[49,2,-135,[4,4278190080]]],1,4],[5,130.01999999999998,54.4]],[2,"question_bg",1,[-137],[[0,-136,[14],15]],[5,490,204],[0,500,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[28,"blockInputEvents",155,2,[[17,0,-138,[25],26],[12,-139]],[4,4278190080],[5,750,1670]],[5,"Base_Music",9,[[0,-140,[49],50]],[5,199,67]],[1,"Slider_Music",9,[[0,-141,[51],52]],[5,84,85],[-70,5,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[5,"Base_Sound",10,[[0,-142,[55],56]],[5,199,67]],[1,"Slider_Sound",10,[[0,-143,[57],58]],[5,84,85],[-70,5,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[5,"Base_Vibration",11,[[0,-144,[61],62]],[5,199,67]],[1,"Slider_Vibration",11,[[0,-145,[63],64]],[5,84,85],[-70,5,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[31,"BACKGROUND_SPRITE",512,12,[[-146,[6,0,45,160,40,-147]],1,4],[5,160,40]],[32,"TEXT_LABEL",512,false,12,[[-148,[18,0,45,2,158,40,-149]],1,4],[5,158,40],[0,0,1],[-78,20,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[33,"PLACEHOLDER_LABEL",512,12,[[-150,[18,0,45,2,158,40,-151]],1,4],[4,4290493371],[5,158,40],[0,0,1],[-78,20,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[50,"New Node",false,[4],[0,0,0],[0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[5,"Main Camera",4,[[51,7,-1,-152]],[5,960,640]],[52,30,30],[1,"advertisementVideo",17,[[0,-153,[4],5]],[5,66,50],[1,1,0,0,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,1]],[53,"第999关",32,false,1,1,33,[10]],[16,"questionLabel",34,[-154],[4,4290362305],[5,450,50.4]],[54,"如何将10L水平分成2份？",30,false,1,1,3,50,[13]],[1,"title",7,[[0,-155,[16],17]],[5,192,49],[0,330,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[16,"promptLabel",7,[-156],[4,4281428931],[5,525,50.4]],[55,60,60,false,1,1,1,3,53,[22]],[35,"shengli",200,2,[-157],[5,530.97,530.97],[0,430,0,0,0,0,1,0.8,0.8,0.8]],[59,"default","animation_loop",0,"animation_loop",55,[27]],[10,"Animation_Title",2,[-158],[5,692,173],[0,460,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[20,"default","gxgg_idle",0,false,false,"gxgg_idle",1,57,[28]],[1,"Animation",2,[[60,"default","animation",0,false,"animation",-159,[29],30]],[5,370,488.03],[0,-151.007,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"icon_xgbsw",2,[[0,-160,[31],32]],[5,221,51],[0,-227.884,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[36,"skeleton",2,[-161],[5,1454.61,1391.99]],[20,"default","animation",0,false,false,"animation",1,61,[33]],[10,"skeleton",2,[-162],[5,1454.61,1391.99],[0,-600,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[61,"default","animation",0,false,"animation",1,63,[34]],[1,"bg_game",3,[[0,-163,[39],40]],[5,605,870],[0,-95.369,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"Title_Setting",3,[[0,-164,[41],42]],[5,91,46],[0,303.684,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"icon_db2",3,[[0,-165,[43],44]],[5,550,528],[0,-31.316,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[1,"icon_1",3,[[0,-166,[45],46]],[5,194,350],[-125,-31.316,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[38,1,0,42,[73]],[56,20,25,false,1,1,43],[57,"Enter text here...",20,25,false,1,1,44,[74]],[62,8,6,12,70,71,69],[9,"Label",512,13,[[13,"跳转",20,false,1,1,1,1,-167,[75]]],[4,4278190080],[5,100,40]],[9,"Label",512,14,[[13,"关闭",20,false,1,1,1,1,-168,[80]]],[4,4278190080],[5,100,40]],[9,"Label",512,15,[[13,"胜利",20,false,1,1,1,1,-169,[85]]],[4,4278190080],[5,100,40]],[37,"log",6,[-170],[4,4278190080],[5,0,31.5],[0,0,0.5],[296.45,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1]],[58,20,25,1,1,76,[90]],[63,4,2,5,18,54,19,20,17]],0,[0,0,1,0,-1,30,0,-2,31,0,-3,16,0,-4,8,0,-5,32,0,-6,34,0,-7,18,0,-8,2,0,-9,5,0,-10,6,0,-1,62,0,-2,64,0,7,56,0,8,58,0,9,21,0,0,2,0,-1,35,0,-2,55,0,-3,57,0,-4,59,0,-5,60,0,-6,61,0,-7,63,0,-8,21,0,0,3,0,-1,65,0,-2,66,0,-3,67,0,-4,68,0,-5,23,0,-6,9,0,-7,10,0,-8,11,0,-9,24,0,0,4,0,0,4,0,10,8,0,11,16,0,12,51,0,13,49,0,14,78,0,15,47,0,0,4,0,-4,78,0,0,4,0,-1,46,0,16,26,0,17,25,0,18,23,0,19,41,0,20,40,0,21,39,0,22,38,0,23,37,0,24,36,0,0,5,0,-1,22,0,25,29,0,26,77,0,27,28,0,28,27,0,29,72,0,0,6,0,-1,12,0,-2,27,0,-3,28,0,-4,29,0,-5,76,0,0,7,0,-1,52,0,-2,19,0,-3,20,0,-4,53,0,0,8,0,0,8,0,-1,17,0,0,9,0,0,9,0,-1,36,0,-2,37,0,0,10,0,0,10,0,-1,38,0,-2,39,0,0,11,0,0,11,0,-1,40,0,-2,41,0,-1,72,0,-1,42,0,-2,43,0,-3,44,0,0,13,0,0,13,0,-1,73,0,0,14,0,0,14,0,-1,74,0,0,15,0,0,15,0,-1,75,0,0,16,0,0,16,0,0,17,0,-1,48,0,0,18,0,0,19,0,0,19,0,0,20,0,0,20,0,0,21,0,0,21,0,0,22,0,0,22,0,0,22,0,0,23,0,0,23,0,0,24,0,-1,25,0,-2,26,0,0,25,0,0,25,0,0,26,0,0,26,0,0,27,0,0,28,0,0,29,0,-1,47,0,0,31,0,0,31,0,0,32,0,-1,33,0,-1,49,0,0,33,0,0,34,0,-1,50,0,0,35,0,0,35,0,0,36,0,0,37,0,0,38,0,0,39,0,0,40,0,0,41,0,-1,69,0,0,42,0,-1,70,0,0,43,0,-1,71,0,0,44,0,0,46,0,0,48,0,-1,51,0,0,52,0,-1,54,0,-1,56,0,-1,58,0,0,59,0,0,60,0,-1,62,0,-1,64,0,0,65,0,0,66,0,0,67,0,0,68,0,0,73,0,0,74,0,0,75,0,-1,77,0,30,45,1,3,4,3,3,5,4,3,45,7,3,18,13,3,27,14,3,28,15,3,29,170],[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,47,56,58,62,64,69],[-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,-1,1,-1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,-1,-1,4,-1,1,-1,-1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,1,-1,-1,-1,-1,1,5,6,-1,-1,1,5,6,-1,-1,1,5,6,-1,-1,1,31,32,33,34,35,36,37,38,4,4,4,4,1],[0,16,0,17,0,18,0,19,0,20,0,0,21,0,0,22,0,23,0,7,0,24,0,0,25,0,8,2,2,2,26,0,27,2,2,0,28,0,8,0,29,0,30,0,31,0,32,0,7,0,3,0,4,0,5,0,3,0,4,0,5,0,3,0,4,0,5,0,33,0,34,0,35,0,0,0,0,1,1,6,0,0,1,1,6,0,0,1,1,6,0,0,36,37,38,39,40,41,42,43,44,45,46,9,9,47]],[[{"name":"prompt_bg","rect":[0,0,703,744],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[703,744],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[48]],[[{"name":"default_sprite_splash","rect":[0,0,2,2],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[2,2],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[49]],[[{"name":"btn_set","rect":[0,0,76,76],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[76,76],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[50]],[[{"name":"bg","rect":[0,0,750,1671],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[750,1671],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[51]],[[{"name":"btn_prompt","rect":[0,0,163,177],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[163,177],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[52]],[[{"name":"title_solutionPrompt","rect":[0,0,192,49],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[192,49],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[53]],[[{"name":"question_bg","rect":[0,0,490,204],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[490,204],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[54]],[[{"name":"default_btn_normal","rect":[0,0,40,40],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[40,40],"capInsets":[12,12,12,12]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[55]],[[{"name":"advertisementVideo_bg","rect":[1,1,53,53],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[55,55],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[56]],[[{"name":"nextLevelBtn","rect":[2,2,353,133],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[357,137],"capInsets":[0,0,0,0]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[57]],[[{"name":"default_editbox_bg","rect":[0,0,40,40],"offset":[0,0],"originalSize":[40,40],"capInsets":[12,12,12,12]}],[0],0,[0],[2],[58]]]]